Hello hello hello friends
welcome once again to Pooja's Matar in today's topic, we will
tell you how to
insure your two wheeler, four wheeler or any type of bike from ICICI Lombard General Insurance.
In this video, friends, you
can do it from CSC digital poster or directly
go to the departmental website of Lombard and click on it,
you
can insure any type of
vehicle, be it a two wheeler or four wheeler
or whatever type of bicycle you have, you can
insure it, so we will give you
this report, after going in, you will see,
after logging in, you have to go here,
after doing service government government, after going to
motor company here,
after going there, you have to see here,
you have to simply click on hearing written ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
after clicking, your new interface
will open like this, see, you have gone here,
see from here, the right to renew is fine, from
here you could do it for two wheeler,
four wheeler, the
mission is of this type of size  And hence
whoever is of this type, you can do it
from here for nude cycle also, on
this occasion, you have to do it from here for the former CO policy for
new graphical nude cycle,
if you are renewing an old vehicle, then on
this occasion you have to
click on the renewal button and you
can do it for this type of vehicle, see, it is a two wheeler,
this is comprehensive insurance, here
taking two wheeler TP TP means third
party insurance, if you
want to do third party insurance for a two wheeler, then you
can click on this button, it is on the two wheeler
tip,
see, it also works like this, the car that
you have given is comprehensive and one
car is third party, this piece is also f-35 means
third party, so you can do whatever you want to do in this, so let's
go to comprehensive, same processor of both,
friends, you can do it
for third party, in third party you spend less money,
so if you want to do it, you should do
comprehensive also, do it from this also
because if the second party will get an accident in the third party,
only that person gets
insurance in this, by
going to the first party  If you have stood then you could
not get it or that is why you should do
comprehensive insurance only, if
you are doing two wheeler or you want to do four wheeler then
let's see here it is less secret for
two wheeler, after this we
will click on get court button, after
clicking on details here
your new interface will open like this, do you want to purchase
tenders for
deposit, if you want to take it at this stage then leave
this button as no,
here simply you have to enter the vehicle number here,
after entering the vehicle number
click on get your details button,
after clicking see your complete details here your
registration date will come here of RTO
office, choose which is your vehicle, where is
my Hero
Honda here your model is
your passion, passion is a
privacy vehicle, here
we will do policy type normal, see
for how many years you want to do it, that too
three aire options are given here, you
can do it as per your wish, that
appointment is here
When is the year of manufacture, the vehicle is 2011 model, I have
put Music and description on it, nothing needs to be entered,
here it has to be done as individual,
okay, if it is company then you can do it on companies,
after that see already open
personal accident news, let it come up with yes button,
national cover can do additional cover,
you will do no, additional trading will do no,
previous insurance policy
details are available, if you have
previous policy details then
click on this button, otherwise click on no,
after that click on get button,
see here the state is missing, choose the state here,
see this policy
starter 12321 Chauhan's
click on the yuktyukt button, it was done now,
after this see here your Idea
ID is gone, by giving your number, the total from the girlfriend will be on the
head, here the engine number, chassis
number automatically comes, simply you have to
enter the name of the nominee,
after that what is the relation of Navmi with you
and after that choose this job of Monica,
after this get  You have to click on the proposal button, you were robbed, you were
robbed, see here there is an option of create new customer, do
this thing,
we have not entered the details of Kayastha number,
see you have to do that for the customer in whose name the car is,
type here the
date of birth of Kayan or
choose the address of Hussain,
choose this landmark near, this
mail ID of the customer
and after that type the pin code or
today again you can choose the mobile number,
enter the email ID,
good wishes,
after that enter the mobile number of the customer
and
a PAN number is optional, Devi Shakti Naveed
can click on the get proposal button,
after that the details done will be visible to you, you have to simply
click on the bye-bye policy button,
see here it is asking for advance feature, simply
click on the proceed button,
here the option of simple payment has come,
see how much interest you are getting in this, it is
₹10 Katra  That in 1181,
through you, you are getting an interest of ₹100 on one ₹10,
so instead of hating, see
friends how to buy a car with this LMB,
you can easily buy a four wheeler car
and you
get commission in it, so if you liked the video then
like and share it, that's all for today's video, we will
meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye